大家好 大家好
hello hello everyone
我是琪雅，希望你们玩得开心。
I'm Kia I hope you guys are having fun
非常感谢你们邀请我
thank you so much for having me
对我来说，能在这里工作是一件非常有意义的事情。
it's a really huge owning for me to be here
我想感谢所有beatcomp
and I would like to sunk all of the beatcomp
组织者，感谢他们让这一切发生
organizers and stuff for making this happen
我知道这有多热
I know how hot it is
组织一个活动
to organize an event up
这种规模
this size
所以非常感谢你们的肉搏会。
so thank you so much for having meat beatcomp
并感谢你们所有人
and thank you all
感谢大家参加这个大型活动
for joining this big event
今天我的演讲是
today my talk is
深入探讨beat press
deep dive into beat press
对于那些不知道beat press是什么的人来说
for those who don't know what beat press is
beat press是一个以节拍为动力的静态网站生成器
beat press is a beat powered static side generator
它可以建立任何类型的静态网站
it can build any kind of static website
在这次演讲中
and with this talk
我将尝试介绍beat press可以做什么
I'll try to introduce what beat press can do
更重要的是
and more importantly
beat press是如何做所有的事情的
how beat press does all of the things it does
然而，在进入讲座之前
however before going to the talk
请允许我介绍一下自己
please let me introduce myself a bit
我是Kia
I'm Kia
我是一名网页设计师，也是一名开发人员
I'm a web designer and also a developer
我是viewjs法庭的成员
I'm viewjs court team member
目前专注于很明显的深度加法
and currently focusing on well obviously deep plus
我在global brain工作
I'm walking at global brain
这是在日本最大的betro资本之一
which is the one of the largest betro capital in Japan
我们在世界各地都有办事处
we have offices around
我们在世界各地都有办事处，并在各地进行创业公司的投资。
world and doing the startup investments everywhere
我很确定有
I'm pretty sure there's
我敢肯定，有很多创业公司的成员也会参加这个活动。
lots of startups members joining this event as well
所以，如果你有任何关于你的业务的很酷的想法
so if you have any cool ideas about your business
请随时在Twitter或其他地方联系我
please feel free to hit me on twitter or
其他地方
somewhere else
我一定会帮助你的
and i'mma be able to help
好的
okay
关于我的事情已经够多了，让我们深入了解一下小麦加。
enough about me let's dive into wheat plus
那么，什么才是真正意义上的beat press呢？
so what is beat press in the false place
节拍新闻
beat press
是一个由节拍和视图驱动的静态网站生成器
is a beat and view powered static site generator
所以你可以用beat建立任何静态网站
so you can build any static website with beat
超快的死亡服务器
super fast death server
而且
and
它可以用markdown写内容
it can write content in markdown
好
well
我认为
I think
许多静态生成器都能做到这一点
many static side generator out there can do this
但我的意思是用markdown写内容
but I mean writing contents in markdown
是一种基本的事情
is kind of basic thing that
所有的静态生成器都能做到
all of the static side generator can do
但是Beat Press也可以
but beat press can too
而且更重要的是
and more importantly
它可以在markdown火里面使用视图组件
it can use view component inside markdown fire
所以如果你看了适当的
so if you view the proper
你可能已经知道了beat press
you might already know about beat press
是非常相似的
which is very similar
或
or
也许我应该说，它与 "拍打 "几乎是一回事。
maybe I should say it's pretty much the same thing as
beat press，但
beat press but
它是建立在webpack之上的
it was built on top of webpack
而vpress是建立在v之上的
where v press is built on v
重点是
the point is
你可以在markdown中使用view组件
that you can use view component inside markdown
并渲染输出
and render output
这些视图组件将在南部被渲染
those view component will get southern side rendered
并成为研究对象
and become study
hml CSS和javascript
hml CSS and javascript
在最后
at the end
所以现在让我们来看看作为你的vtres的基本用途
so now let's see the basic use as your vtres
在本讲座中
in this talk
我不打算解释每个功能的
I'm not planning to explain each features of
的每个功能，而是
wheat press but rather
我们要谈的是小麦压榨机如何
we like to talk about how wheat press
做所有这些功能
do all of those features
但它是如何与节拍发生兴趣的，以及它是如何使用节拍的
but and how it interests with beat and how it uses beat
他们完成了静态方面的生成
they accomplish static side generation
但要做到这一点，我们需要有基本的
but to do so we need to have basic
我们需要对beat press能做什么有基本的了解
understanding of what beat press can do
所以让我们快速浏览一下
so let's quickly go through
beat press提供的基本功能
the basic features that beat press offers
最基本的beat press设置是这样的
the very minimum beat press setup will look like this
首先，你创建你的项目文件夹
first you create your project folder
然后放上邻近的软件包和索引MD
then put package adjacent and index MD
你可以看到索引MD是一个根文件
as you can see the index MD is a root file
你现在可以在这个Mark中写任何东西
and you you write anything in this Mark now
然后你安装peak press p npm
and then you install peak press p npm
然后通过npx v d press命令运行b press。
then run b press through like npx v d press command
然后你会得到这个网站
and then you get thiswebsite
在你的电脑上运行后
after running on your orc machine
你可以看到那个MACDON文件已经过去了
you kind of see that macdon file got past
有一个标题是server one和level
there's a heading server one and level
2与它的内容
2 with its contents
甚至
even
甚至是这个单一的macdon文件
even this single macdon file
它也有这个概要的特点
it comes with this outline features
在这里你可以看到在页面的右边
where you can see at the right side of the page
我们有
we have
在页面的右上方有明暗开关
light and darkmore switch on top right of the page
所以顺便说一下
so by the way
即使是没有冲突的单一标记文件，它也看起来
even just no conflict single markdown file it looks
很好的奶油色和美丽
pretty cream and beautiful
所以，也许这在你的简历上效果很好
so maybe this works pretty well on your resume
网站上也是如此简单
site was something simple like that
但在这种设置下，我们只有一个单页
but with this set up we only have one single page
而这对大多数网站来说是不够的
and that's not enough for most of the website
所以你可以按照
so you can follow
通过添加冲突来定制你的网站
customize your website by adding conflicts
要做到这一点，将config js放到vte press文件夹下。
to do so place config js to under the vte press folder
在这个文件中，你可以添加许多配置，如
and in this file you can add many configs such as
网站标题语言描述
site title languages description
这些是网站的元数据
these are the metadata for the website
你可以添加 nutwire config
you can add nutwire config
这是网站的页眉
which is the header of the website
你可以添加侧边栏
and you can add sidebar
显示在页面的左侧
which is shown on the left side of the page
做完所有的配置后
and after doing all of the configuration
并在文件夹中添加更多的文件
and adding more files inside folders
最后你会得到网站
and finally you get website
像这样的东西
something look like this
这就是境外
this is the offshore
文档的网站
documentation website for beat class
你可以看到
as you can see
这里有一个侧边的导航按钮
there's a sideburn navigation such button
和标题，你有不同的导航
and header you have different navigation
你甚至可以添加广告
you can even add ads
我把它隐藏在屏幕中
I'm hiding it in the screen
但在右下角你可以看到
but on the right bottom of the corner you can see
你可以把这样的广告
you can put the advertisement that such
现在deep press带有这个默认的水槽
now deep press comes with this default sink
它专注于创建文档网站
which is focused on creating documentation website
这就是为什么Wheat Press提供的功能
which is why wheat press offers features
所需要的
that required by
大多数的文档网站都是默认的
most of the documentation website by default
比如说有侧面
such as having side was
和显示页面的轮廓
and displaying the outline of the page
然而，但同样
however but again
小麦网是一个静态的侧面生成器
wheat press is a static side generator
而不是一个文档网站生成器
and not a documentation website generator
所以它只是恰好是目前的主要用途
so it just happens to be that the current main usage
是用来创建文档的，因为你知道markdown
is for creating documentation because you know markdown
在建立文档方面是相当不错的，对吗？
is quite good at building documentations right
但是
but
默认的缝隙是集中在添加裂缝
the default seam is focused on adding fissures
有关的文件网站
related to documentation website
因为这
because of that
但是
but
它可以在里面使用任何视图组件
it can use any view component inside it
事实上
in fact
所有的默认缝隙都是用视图组件构建的
all of the default seam is built with view component
所以
so
我们是暴徒的例子，这并不是一个真正的文件
we are mob example which is not really a documentation
的例子
for example
我忘了说，但深度网站也是
I forgot to mention but deep website is also
用beat press构建的
built with beat press
而这是有意义的，因为Beat网站是
and it makes sense because beat website is
deet文档网站
deet documentation website
对，所以我们想使用beat press
right so we want to use beat press
但在Beat网站上
but on beat website
你看到的页面，如团队页面
you see pages like team page
这个页面不是一个自定义页面
well this page is not a custom page
而是包含在 vietpa 的默认场景中
but rather included in vietpa's default scene
但要写这样的页面是很难的
but it's quite hard to write this kind of page
用markdown编写
with markdown
对
right
所以我们用视图组件来做这个
so we use view component for this
这个页面的源代码是这样的
the source code of this page looks like this
这实际上是一个markdown文件
this is actually a markdown file
在这里你没有发现任何markdown的语法
there is no markdown syntax you find here
但你真的可以把markdown内容
but you can really mix markdown content
和视图组件在一起
and view component together
在这里你可以看到
here you see
我们导入视图组件并使用它就像
we import view components and using it just as if
这是一些单一的文件组件
this is a few single file component
所以同样，第一个默认的模拟是专注于
so again the first default sim is focused on
创建文档网站
creating documentation website
你可以使用beat press来创建任何研究网站
you can use beat press to create any study website
它不一定是一个文件
it doesn't have to be a documentation
另一个例子是这个
another example will be this one
这是我最近在我的公司建立的一个网站
this is a website I build recently at my company
它没有使用任何beat press的默认场景
it doesn't use any of beat press default scene
看起来是完全原创的
the seeming is completely original
但它仍在使用deep press
but it's still using deep press
所以如果你是一个
so if you are a
视图开发人员，如果你想拥有静态网站
view developer and if you want to have static website
并使用正确的视图内容
and use view right content
deep press可能是你的选择之一
deep press might be one of your choice
即使是对于那些不属于文件的东西
even for things that are not a documentation
现在我希望你
now I hope you
对Beatrice的功能有了基本的了解
have a basic understanding of what Beatrice can do
现在让我们来看看
now let's go into
如何
how
Beatrice是如何行走的
Beatrice walks
再一次
again
我不打算介绍Beatrice的功能
I'm not going through the features of beat press
而是
but rather
而是要看看Beat Press如何实现这些功能
looking to how beat press enables those features
以及它如何使用节拍来实现这些功能
and how it uses beat to do so
喜欢做任何beat press做的事情
like to do anything that beat press does
现在，beat press已经深深地融入到视图中，因为
now beat press is deeply integrated to view because
beat press的整个要点
the whole point of beat press
是
is
它的小麦和视图驱动的多余的发生器
its wheat and viewpowered set excess generator
但是
however
正如你已经知道的，小麦并没有被锁定在视图中
as you already know wheat is not locked in the view
你可以将小麦用于许多
you can use wheat with many
许多其他的javascript框架，如react
many other javascript frameworks such as react
solid belt等。
solid belt and such
对，所以通过学习beat press如何使用视图
right so by learning how beat press uses view
你可以将同样的技术
you may apply the same technique
也可以应用于其他框架
for other frameworks too
这就是我希望你们能学到的东西
and that's what I'm hoping you guys would learn
和
and
你知道的，创造一些很棒的软件
you know create some awesome software
并使世界变得更美好
and make the world better
为了了解海滩是如何运作的，首先
in order to understand how beach first works
你可以做的最精确的事情是查看
the most precise thing you can do is look
源代码
into the source code
这就是这个
which is this
好的
well
有很多文件，但你只需要看一下
there are lots of files but you only have to look into
源码边界
source border
但即使对我来说，它
but even for me it
是一种压倒性的通过
was kind of overwhelming to go through
像每个文件
like each file
事实上，我正打算在我的文本编辑器上打开
in fact I was planning to open
在我的文本编辑器上打开这个源边界
this source border on my text editor
并向大家展示
and show everyone
大量的源代码，并通过像
a lot of source code and go through like
一行又一行
lines by lines
但好在
but well
这比我想象的要难
it was harder than I thought
所以有很多的代码
so there are lots of codes
所以我将挑选
so instead I'll pick
重要部分的代码并解释
important part of the code and explain
尽可能的简单
as simple as much as I can
它变得有点抽象了
it becomes a bit more abstract
但我希望你能得到更多
but I hope you get more
清楚区别是什么
glass idea of what difference is doing
在你知道它的作用之后
and after you know what it does
如果你通过实际的源代码
and if you go through the actual source code
你会得到更多
you will get more
更好的
better
理解
understanding
所以我做了一个下降的片断，以便
so I made the falling slice so
以便与
to match
尽可能地与实际的源代码结构相一致
the actual source code structure as much as possible
我希望你能更容易找到
I hope you will make easier for you to
找到相应的代码
locate corresponding code
一旦
once after
解决幻灯片的问题
you solve the slides
因此，核心组件
so the core components
beatfress有两个大的
beatfress has 2 big
组件，即客户端代码和底层代码
components which is client side code and subside code
客户端代码是在客户端文件夹中
client code is in the client folder
旁侧代码在节点文件夹中
and savaside code is on node folder
客户端代码
client code
Lonzon浏览器和Sovicide代码在Lonzon服务端。
lonzon browsers and sovicide code lonzon service side
但它是一个静态网站生成器
but it's a static site generator
因此，在生产环境中，没有拍子的压力。
so in production environment there's no beat press
我应该说，也许在我的节拍萨瓦上有萨维尔。
saville up on lombing my beat sava I should say maybe
但是，通常情况下，子集
but so usually the subset
代码是指在你的岩石机器上运行的代码
code means that code runs on your rock machine
在客户端的炮灰里面
inside client fodder
我们有炮灰
we have fodder
2种不同类型的客户端代码
2 different types of client code
一个叫做app，另一个叫做c
one is called app and the other it's c
应用程序代码是核心的拍拍贷代码
app code is the core beat press code
它处理所有的基本功能，如路由
it handles all basic features such as routing
带价格的热门模块
hot module with price men
深度工具整合
depth tools integration
和管理网站的元数据
and managing the site metadata
加载上下文等
loading context and such
另一方面，缝合代码在本例中被命名为缝合
seam code in other hand is in this case named seam
默认的
default
是一个缝合的具体代码
is a seam specific code
所有的冲突
all of the conflict that
只有与接缝有关的冲突才会被用在这个代码中。
only relates the seam will be used in this code only
因此，如果你想建立你自己的网站
so if you want to build your own website
使用场景的结果切割
result cut using the scene
这些都不是simka
none of this simka
将会被学习
will be learning
所以我们可以完全删除这个文件夹
so we can completely delete this folder
这样就可以毫无问题地行走了
and this press would walk without a problem
现在了解一些应用程序如何工作的最佳方式
now best way to understand how some application works
是通过目标
is the goal through
一步一步地从入口处开始
step by step from the entry point
我的意思是
by that I mean
如果我们想创建一个启动兴奋的发电机
if we want to create a start excite generator
我们需要在开始时做什么，比如
what we need to do at the beginning like
我们如何开始我们的深度
how do we start the depths of our
或如何
or how
我们可以建立一个代码
can we build a code
好的
well
我们需要cli命令
we need cli command
我们需要有
we need to have
一些命令来开始建立网站，这意味着
some command to start building the website that means
beat press实际上是
beat press is actually
一个cli应用程序
a cli application
所以Beat Press有几个命令，主要的命令是
so beat press has several commands that main ones does
主要的有以下几个
main ones are these ones
wheat press depth and wheat pressed
建立
built
死亡命令将启动一个使用小麦的死亡服务器
death command will boot a death server using wheat
和wield命令将构建生产构建
and wield command will build the production build
所以让我们来看看
so let's check out
当我们执行这些命令时会发生什么
what happens when we execute these commands
这些命令可能会在哪个文件中运行
possible which file will these commands run
实际上，它在bean文件夹中，看起来像这样
actually it's in the bean folder and it looks like this
好了，这就是它
well that's it
这是一个简单的js文件
it's a simple js file
它正在加载dist文件夹下的cli.js。
and it's loading cli.js under dist folder
现在这个文件夹是生成编译文件的地方
now this folder is where compiled file gets generated
因为speedpress是用脚本类型写的
because speedpress is written in type script
所以实际的cli文件在souls known文件夹下。
so the actual cli file is under souls known folder
让我们看看它是什么样子的
and let's see how that looks
它看起来像这样
it looks like this
好了，你不必担心这么多的
well you don't have to worry so much about
细节，因为这些只是处理用户
details because these are just handling users
cliinput和
cliinput and
但现在我们可以看到
but now we can see
此刻实际的命令在做什么
what the actual command is doing at the moment
现在让我们看看死命令在做什么
now let's see what's dead command is doing
它在做这个
it's doing this
好的
okay
所以第一行是dev命令，对吗？
so the first line is the dev command right
它所做的主要事情是创建一个开发
the main thing it does is creating a dev
服务器并启动它
server and starting it
它看起来像
it looks like
它还在做更多的事情
it's doing more
但让我们把重点放在开发生存的迹象上。
but let's focus on dev survival signs here
它创建新的郊区并启动
it creates new suburb and starting
好的，那么这个创建发展的郊区是怎么来的？
ok so where does this create dev suburb is coming from
它来自于
it comes from
斜线节点萨瓦TS火
slash node sava TS fire
它看起来像这样
it looks like this
我没有在这里展示所有的东西
I'm not showing everything here
但请跟着我，我将会
but stay with me I'm gonna
我将
I'll
通过它
go through it
也许它是
maybe it does
主要是做两件事
mainly it does 2 things here
一
one
它解决了冲突
it resolves the conflict
因为我们需要应用任何冲突
well because we need to apply any conflict
用户定义的
users defined
以便
so that
第一件事是解决冲突
the first thing we do is to resolve the conflict
我不打算研究冲突在哪里，因为
I'm not going to look into conflict far where because
它所做的一切就是
all that all it does is
试图为冲突设置默认值
tries to set default value for the conflict
如果有任何用户输入的信息
if any user input is given
它就会使用这个值
it will use that
并使用该值代替默认值
and use that instead of the default one
但是因为有很多冲突
but because there's lots of conflict
冲突雾是相当巨大的
the conflict fog is quite huge
但它所做的很简单
but what it does is simple
它只是降低了所有用户的配置
it just lowells all users config
并设置了最终的配置对象
and set up the final config object
的最终配置对象。
that
在整个应用程序的代码中使用
should be used throughout the app code
现在，下一个问题是
now the next one is
它做的下一件事是这样的
next thing it does is this
这实际上是它做的最后一件事
which is actually the last thing it does
它创建了一个开发夏日
it creates a dev summer
现在你可以看到，它正在调用一个创建
now you can see that it's calling a creat
beat summer，这很重要
beat summer which is important
从节拍来看，这实际上是它
from beat this is actually it
它正在调用beat summer
it's a calling beat summer
它在这个文件中没有做别的事情
and there's nothing else it does in this file
我们应该关注的部分是这里
the part we should be focusing is here
插件将传递到缝隙中
plugins will pass into the sew
所以在这里你可以看到，这个插件被命名为
so here you can see that this plugin is named
create v plugin
因此，从本质上讲，Wheat Press只是一个Wheat插件
so essentially wheat press is just a wheat plug in
它做所有的事情，作为小麦的插件
it does all of the things as wheat plug in
现在你也可以看到它是如何
and also now you can see how it's
Howie它是如何
Howie how it is
它是以编程方式创建beatsuba的。
is it create beatsuba programmatically right
你只要从beat中导入creasava
you just import createsava
并运行它
from beat and run it
你就可以创建你自己的节拍了
and you can create your own beats up
所以，如果你想创建任何像
so if you want to create any like
自定义命令，可以启动beatsaval
custom command that can boot up beatsaval
这就是你现在要做的
this is how you do it now
让我们进入创建按下插件的功能
let's go into create the press plugin function
它的作用是什么？
what does it do
现在
now
这个功能
this function
该插件功能来自于灵魂斜线鼻子插件
the plugin function comes from soul slash nose plugin
边界 现在从这里开始，水槽变得有趣和
border now from here sinks get interesting and
当然，更复杂的是
more complicated of course
现在，这就是实际的Soulsco
now this is the actual soulsco
但你可以看到
but as you can see
而且我没有足够的空间来展示
and I don't have enough space to show
旧的实际代码
old actual code
所以让我们在这里删掉一些冷门的东西，使之简单化
so let's cut off some cold here and make it simple
这里的主要目标是创建V
the main goal here is to create v
插件
plugging
所以这段代码看起来像这样
so that code looks like this
现在v plugging是一个对象
now v plugging is an object
有
with
你可以添加很多配置
lots of configuration you can add
你可以找到所有的文档和小麦的网站
you can find all of the documentation and wheat website
沿着这条路线，他们有什么样的选择
along which like what kind of options they had
但在这里
but here again
让我们把注意力集中在对新闻界重要的事情上
let's focus on what matters for beat press
当我们插入
as we plug in
我们要做的是
what we want to do is
将一个吉利姆的标记文件
transform a gilliam markdown file
转换成我们
to something that we
可以处理的
can handle
因为在默认情况下，V对markdown没有任何作用
because as the default v does nothing for markdown
野生的吧
wild right
所以如果有一些markdown文件进来了
so if some markdown comes in
我们需要做的是
we need to do well
不管是什么节拍的新闻想做什么
whatever beat press want to do with that
做什么
wile to do
所以我们在录像带上有转换选项
so we have transform option in vidfording
它应该是这样的
which should look like this
在这里，我切断了不重要的寒冷
here I am cutting off not that important cold
而只显示重要的部分
and only shown the important ones
但在这里
but here it
你可以看到，它正试图处理传入的文件
you can see that it's trying to handle incoming file
false east 语句
the false east statement
检查火的扩展名是否为点视图
checks if the fire extension is dot view
不是
not
好了，首先打败了Lendo的markdown
well beat first lendo's markdown
但你也可以直接处理视图文件
but you can also handle view file directly too
所以如果有任何bu文件进来
so if any bu file comes in
不是macno fire而是view文件进来了
not macno fire but the view file comes in
我们就会处理它
we'll just handle it
我们也只是处理这个
we just handle that too
你看，有一个处理客户端js的函数
you see there is a process client js function
这是一个处理任何用户定义的
this is the function that processes any user defined
在文件中工作的javascript代码
javascript code working in the file
并添加到hashma中
and add to the hashma
所以我们可以用这个函数来渲染渲染的输出
so we can use that with rendering rendered output
在最后的输出上
on the final output
但这并不是真正的大事情
but it's not really the huge things
不要对这个问题太过担心
don't worry so much about this
接下来的语句是寻找
the next statement is looking for
MD的扩展，也就是markdown
MD extension which is the markdown
在这种情况下
in this case
传入的文件实际上是markdown文件
incoming file is actually the markdown file
在这种情况下，我们需要暂停这个markdown文件
in this case we need to pause the markdown file
以便以后处理该文件
in order to process the file later on
我们如何做到这一点，就是暂停markdown文件
how we do this is to pause markdown file
变成查看源代码
into view source code
然后把它传递给海滩流水线
and then pass it down to the beach pipeline
之后，我们就可以处理视图文件，查看其视图插件
after that we can handle view file view its view plugin
所以我们在这里所要做的就是转换markdown文件
so all we have to do here is transform markdown file
并使其成为
and make it
视图文件
view file
为了做到这一点，我们有这个markdown到view的函数
to do that we have this markdown to view function
该函数返回view slc对象和view source对象
which returns view slc object view source object
视图源对象通过进程客户端获得
and the view source object get past the process client
js文件
js file
就像我们用视图文件转换时一样
as the same as we did when transforming with view file
实际上这就是B的关键部分
actually this is the key part of b
另外它还能处理markdown
plus it handles markdown
现在让我们来看看markdown to view文件有什么作用
now let's go see what markdown to view file does
markdown to view命令的实际名称是
the actual name of markdown to view command
的返回函数是由
is the return function from
创建markdown到视图的渲染函数
create markdown to view render function
现在，这个名字很长，但却被处理得很好
now this long name but is quite processed
这个函数返回可以暂停markdown的函数
this function returns function that can pause markdown
考虑到用户环境
taking user context into account
现在它又是非常复杂的
now again it's very complicated
而且看起来有很多事情要做
and looks like many things are going on
但让我们来看看这个目标的一个重要部分
but let's look at an important part of this goal
第一个名字是这样的
the first one name is this
创建markdown渲染
create markdown render
这个函数
this function
是创建一个纯粹的markdown渲染函数
is creating a pure markdown render function
以后可以实际使用
that can later used actually
贷出markdown的康普顿
lender the markdown Compton
这意味着将markdown转换成HTML
which means convert markdown into HTML
让我们看看它是怎样的
let's see how it looks like
这就是这个函数
this is the function
这个函数看起来
this function looks
非常简单，我要说的是
very simple I will say
你可以看到，它正在创建一个新的markdown实例
you can see that it's creating a new markdown instance
markdown eat instance
和markdown hit
and markdown hit
是非常著名的用于javascript的markdown possum
is very famous markdown possum for javascript
我们可以把它用在它身上
and we press use it to it
它所做的就是创建一个新的markdown hit实例
all it does is creating a new markdown hit instance
并添加了很多的markdown插件
and adds a lots of markdown plugins
正如你所看到的，它是一个很大的MD。
as you can see it is a lot of MD
在它的调用中使用函数
use function in its call
这些都是为markdown添加的插件游戏
these are adding plug games to markdown
负鼠
possum
许多插件都是常用的
many plugins are usual
许多插件
many plugins
我使用你的markdown插件并不特别打压
I use your markdown plugins not special to beat press
比如说高亮线
such as highlight line
高亮线插件高亮
highlighting line plug highlight
行插
the line plugging
插件
plugin
突出显示冷块
highlights the cold block
它是用西基
it's using siki
作为一个插件
as a plugin
我想在这里提到的特别的插件是
the special one that I would like to mention here
是组件插件
is component plugin
你可以看到，它是一个非常快速的插件。
that you can see at the very fast plugin to be added
这个插件处理Marcon里面的视图组件
this plugin handles view component inside marcon
火
fire
它允许在Marcon里面调用视图组件
it allows view component called inside marcon
文件上的内容。
file on the excurate
这个插件
this plugin
实际上是发布了一个不同的软件包，叫做MD
is actually published a different package called MD
在超视图
at hyper view
有很多不同的特定视图
there's a lot of different view specific
以及在这里发布的插件
and plugins published here
所以如果你打算创建一个使用
so if you are planning to create soccer that uses
视图的markdown程序，请查看它。
markdown procing with view please check it out
它使用很酷的技术来处理视图文件
it uses cool technique to handle view file
而如果你想为其他的
and if you are trying to create process for other
框架（如react）创建流程
frameworks like react
我敢肯定，你可以在这个包上找到很酷的想法
I'm pretty sure you can find cool ideas on this package
以便你也能应用于这些火焰标记
so that you can apply to those flame marks as well
现在让我们回到插件的代码中来
now let's get back to the plugin code
请记住这就是我们离开的地方
remember here is where we left off
我们已经创建了markdown passer
we've created markdown passer
还有很多事情要做
there's still lots of things going on
但有几件事我想指出来
but there are a few things that I want to point out
这是一个简单但有趣的技术应用
which is simple but interesting technique to apply
当把markdown传递给实际的ismel输出时
when passing the markdown to actual ismel output
在同一个文件中
in same file
过去我们调用markdown函数，我们在这里创建了一个区域
past we call markdown function we've created area here
现在这个hml变量包含了过去的
now this hml variable contains past
markdown文件
markdown file
而这里
and here
我们实际上创建了视图源对象
we actually creates view source object
记住
remember
这就是我们从这个函数返回的对象
this is the object we return from this function
这样它就能通过beat
so that it gets past the beat
并由Beat处理这个对象
and beat handles this object
作为一个视图火。
as a view fire
有几件事
there's a few thing
它没有
it doesn't which
我没有经历过
I didn't go through
比如它传递注入的页面数据代码之类的东西
like it's passing the injected page data code and stuff
但重要的部分是
but the important part is
有一个模板字符串
that there is template string
这一个
this one
所以这里做的是什么呢？
so what's what is doing here
是通过模板标签内的HTML传递的
is passing passing past HTML inside the template tag
因为在视图文件中
because in view file
你把所有的HTML都包在模板标签里了
you wrap all the HTML cold inside template tag
所以它在这里做了什么
so what it does here
是试图创建一个实际的视图文件
is that trying to create a actual view file
这对那些熟悉beat的人来说可能是显而易见的。
this might be obvious for someone with
熟悉beat的人来说是显而易见的。
familiar with beat
的人来说是显而易见的，但从这段代码中可以得到一个很好的启示
but this is a good takeaway from this code
基本上
basically
我们想尽可能地击败处理代码
we want to beat the handle code as much as possible
而且我们知道
and we know that
beat可以处理视图代码
beat can handle view code
所以我们在这里所要做的就是把什么
so all we need to do here is to convert what
转化为视图代码
transform markdown fall into view code
转换成Beat能够理解的视图代码
that beat can understand
这意味着如果你创建
that means if you create
一些自定义的beat程序，通过
some custom beat program that passes
我不知道它是否是markdown以外的东西
I don't know if it's something other than markdown
这里有同样的逻辑目标
the same logic goals here
你得到你想转换的文件
you get the file you want to convert
然后将其转换为远处的格式
then transform it to the far format
在这里，Beat可以理解
where beat can understand
然后其他的事情就由beat来处理了
then everything else will be handled by beat
只是
just
记住这一点
remember this
现在我们有能力
now we're capable
处理markdown文件
of handling markdown file
现在我们需要向客户报告索引 hml
now we need to report index hml to the client
这是在这里
which is down here
现在，在没有更多节拍的应用中
now in no more beat application
你将会有index hml文件
you would have index hml file
在你的项目文件夹下作为一个入口点
under your project folder as an entry point
但在vtpls中我们没有index hml
but in vtpls we don't have index hml
所以我们需要创建它并把它送回给客户
so we need to create it and send it back to the client
所以
so
我们用solve a metalware来交互响应
we use solve a metalware to interact the response
并送回这个空的hml
and send back this empty hml
记住这是死亡的夏天
remember this is death summer
所以它不是一个生产构建
so it's not a production build
所以我们所需要的是相当多的空索引hml内容
so all we need is pretty much empty index hml content
和客户端可以失败的内容
and the content that client can fail
在数据的西部
in the west of the data
似乎是元数据，如网站的标题等。
seems like metadata such as title of the
网站的标题之类的
site and such
beat press创建了一个4 hml，其中包括
beat press creates a 4 hml with
所有的内容都是在生产构建中呈现的
all of the content rendered on production build
但在死亡之夏，我们不需要这样做
but in death summer we don't need to do that
除此以外，还有其他事情
and other thing other than this
beat press有更多的背景
beat press has many more context
来处理诸如热模块替换之类的事情。
to handle things like hot module replacement and
但在这里，我的时间有点不够用了，所以
such but here I'm kind of going short of the time so
让我们转到客户端的代码
let's move to the client side code
这里
here
你可以随时查看源代码并学习
you can always look into the source code and learn
更高级的技术。
about more advanced technique after
以后
later on
所以，一旦我们知道现在的服务器端是
so once we know that now the server side is
返回这个索引hml
returning this index hml
我们在客户端所做的
the client side what we do
是比较直接的
is more straightforward
我想说
I would say
好吧，这个冰冷的东西本身是有点复杂的
well the cold itself is a bit complicated
但它所做的是创建新的视图。
but what it does is it creates new view up
这里你可以看到应用程序
here you can see app that
mount方法，这是
mount method which is
视图的方式，将视图组件安装到dom上
view way of mounting view component to the dom
这没什么特别的，这是一个播放视图的应用程序
it's nothing special this is a playing view app
没有创建拍子，也没有类似的东西。
there's no create beat press up or something like that
它只是一个视图
it's just a view
我们把所有的东西都包起来
well we are wrapping everything
在浏览器中的每一个语句
on in browser each statement here
因为beat fresh是
because beat fresh is the
南侧
southern side
我是说南边的渲染
I mean southern side rendering
在生产模式下的应用，它将会运行
application right in production mode it's gonna run
在太阳能尺寸上的光盘人，所以这只在债务上着陆
disc man on solar size so this only lands on debts
然而，向上的内容
however the up content
我们安装的向上的内容
up contents that we mounting
有凹陷的厚重特征
has depressed thick features
它看起来像这样
and it looks like this
它正在创造一个客户端更响亮的声音
it's creating an client side louder
添加默认的组件，如不磅组件
adding default components such as not pound component
它正在注入一些深层的新闻特定数据
it's injecting some deep press specific data
到子组件之类的
to the child components and such
但从这里
but from here
因为你已经在节拍上完成了所有繁重的工作
because you've done all heavy lifting on beatside
在服务器端
on server side
我的意思是
I mean
这只是一个简单的客户端
this is just a simple client side
我的意思是，比如说
by that I mean for example
我们不在客户端上传递马克，因为
we don't pass Mark down on client sidebecause
因为它已经在南侧完成了
it's already done on south side
所以客户端的代码就像
so the client code walks as if
有一个固定的视图文件已经完成了
there's a fixed view file written done
写入
written
到实际的文件系统中
to the actual file system
而这与从文件系统中加载这些固定视图文件是一样的
and it's same as loading those fixed view file
从文件系统中
from the file system
对
right
而在最后
and at last
这是个接缝文件
this is the seam file
它正在滚动默认的
it's rolling the default
缝作为默认的视图组件
seam as the default view component
它看起来像这样
which looks like this
这是比act文件更普通的视图文件
this is even more plain view file than act file
这只是一个典型的视图组件
this is just a typical view component
有很多槽和很多东西
there's lots of slots and so many things
为什么呢，因为有很多自定义的东西
why on because there are many customization
你可以用默认的缝隙来做
you can do with the default seam
但它仍然只是一个
but still it's just a
播放污垢
playing defile
这是一个默认的缝隙
this is a default seam
所以从这里开始，这些代码都不重要了
so from here on none of these codes matter
如果你想先拥有自己的自定义节拍
if you would like to have your own custom beat first
缝隙中没有包括核心功能
seam no core feature is included here
所以
so
如果你不太关心
if you don't care so much about how
默认接缝是如何创建的
default seam is created
你就可以忽略所有的场景
you can just ignore all of the scene
hydrant default folder
而你可以直接查看app文件夹，看看它在做什么。
and you can just look into app folder and see
它在做什么
what it's doing
现在，抱歉我跳过了客户端的很多沙子
now sorry I skipped lots of sands on client side
但我有点
but I'm kind of
越来越少的时间，所以
getting short on time so
但我希望你能得到一些关于beat
but I hope you are getting some idea on how beat
按键是如何运行的，以及它是如何与beat整合的。
press walks and how it's integrated with beat
所以让我们进入VED的最后一个大命令
so let's go into the final big command that ved has
这就是
which is
构建命令
build command
这个命令将建立一个最终的静态hml文件
this command will build a final static hml file
当它被切除时
when it gets excubed
这就是构建功能的样子
this is how build function looks like
再说一遍，这很复杂
once again well it's complicated
现在，对于构建
now for build
我们要做的和以前差不多
what we want to do is pretty much the same as before
我们想暂停markdown
we want to pause markdown
并最终将其输出到HTML
and finally output it on HTML
而不是从v的深度返回输出的hmm
and instead of returning the output hmm from v depths
或者我们想输出它
or we want to output it
到文件系统中作为一个静态文件
to file system as a static file
要做到这一点，我们需要渲染它
to do so we need to render it
这就是为什么我们在这个构建命令中加入了渲染函数
and that's why we have render function
在这个构建命令中
inside this build command
渲染函数看起来像这样
the render function looks like this
这里它
here it
通过传入文件的方式获得渲染对象
gets the render object by passing in the file pass
因为我们要渲染所有的页面，对吗？
because we want to render all pages right
所以在承诺的所有函数中
so instead inside promised all function
我们传递所有的页面
we pass all of the pages
现在是实际的渲染函数
now the actual render function
在节点中建立渲染TS文件
inside node builds render TS file
在这里，我们定义了我们如何借出权力
here we define how we lend the giving power
和以往一样
again as always
有很多事情要做，但重要的部分是这样的
lots of things going on but an important part is this
现在
now
它看起来更简单，只是把HTML渲染成一个字符串
it seems more simple it just rendering HTML as a string
body标签中的内容变量
the content variable inside the body tag
是从文件中得到的内容
is the content got
从文件中渲染出来的内容
rendered from the file
你可以看到它被包裹在id为app的dip中
as you can see it's wrapped inside dip with id of app
这意味着这就是视图将被安装的dip
which means this is the dip that view will mount on
一旦我们得到这个
once we get this
hml的字符串
string of hml
我们需要做的是
we need to do is
我们需要做的是把它渲染到文件系统上
what we need to do is to render it to the file system
并且我们使用1
and we use 1/1 module from node to do that
null
well I've skipped so many coals for example
it also output like js and CSS chunks
null
so it creates
and also it creates like sub folders and such
null
but I think we get the idea
of what we're trying to do here
null
we're just
trying to lender a file
null
into a string
and this save it as playing a Gemini file
null
now if you find
anything that interest you
null
please go into the actual source code of beat press
and by focusing on how it uses beat
null
and how it handles incoming files
we will learn so much about
null
how
beat pliing walks
null
I've picked important part of the code
but at the same time I'd skipped lots of sense as well
null
but
I hope you got some idea
null
on what big plugin
would look like and I hope
null
it made you more familiar on writing
beat plugin
null
because beat press is a stand alone cli application
but as I shown
null
beat press is wiggly actually is a beat plugin
and also it's one of the official big project that
null
view community manages
so if you're looking for a weight
长久以来健康创建的节拍插件
long health create beat plugin
或者寻找一个关于节拍插件可以做什么的想法
or looking for an idea of what beat plugin can do
我认为beat press是其中一个软件
I think beat press is one of the software
你可能想了解一下它
you might want to look into it
这也是一个很好的索菲亚，可以让你的文档更丰富。
also it's good Sofia to ride your documentation
或创建静态网站也是如此。
or create static website too so yeah
请看一下v press
please check out the v press
非常感谢您的观看
thank you so much for watching
如果你有任何问题，我是Kia，我们只是想打个招呼。
I'm Kia if you have any question we just want to say hi
我在微博上一直是开放的，请告诉我。
I'm always open on twitter sojust let me know
非常感谢，我希望你继续享受
thanks so much and I hope you keep enjoying the
其他的活动
rest of the event
非常感谢
thanks so much